Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Motion Pictures
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, motion pictures
1966-2008
RU 840
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
214.42
(1,052 boxes)
The materials consist of video recordings, notes, statements, motion picture film, stock film, sound tracks, and magnetic tapes used in Office of Public Affairs (formerly Public Information) productions documenting Yale. Many of the video recordings in Accession 2009-A-156 are commercially produced by entities external to Yale.
Yale University. Office of Public Affairs
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 48-B (YRG 48-B), Yale audiovisual records and collections.
Existence and Location of Copies
Copies of the final films produced for distribution are catalogued individually.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of video recordings, notes, statements, motion picture film, stock film, sound tracks, and magnetic tapes used in Office of Public Affairs (formerly Public Information) productions documenting Yale. Many of the video recordings in Accession 2009-A-156 are commercially produced by entities external to Yale.
Motion pictures (visual works); Videotapes; Yale University. Office of Public Affairs
- Films produced by the Office of Public Affairs, circa 1970-1979; Accession 1979-A-009
  - "Transition Year"
    - Sync rolls
      - Giamatti-Goldstein: SR 12 (Box 1)
      - O&M, SR16, 1978 (Box 1)
      - Sports -Harvard/Yale, SR 4 (Box 1)
      - Graduation, SR 14, 1978 (Box 1)
      - Jamboree, 1B (Box 1)
      - Crew, SR 3, 1977 (Box 1)
      - AYA luncheon, SR 6 (Box 1)
      - Graduation, 1978 (Box 1)
      - Graduation, 1978 (Box 2)
      - Creactive Arts & Music Class, SR 2 (Box 2)
      - Mad Dog Blues, SR 7 (Box 2)
      - Scoup Jackson, SR 13 (Box 2)
      - Scully, Silliman grad, SR 8 (Box 2)
      - Yale Daily News banquet, SR 11 (Box 2)
      - Yale/Harvard game, SR 5 (Box 2)
      - Classrooms (Box 2)
      - Strikers, Yale Daily News, SR 1 code JC (Box 2)
      - Students moving in; license plates (Box 3)
      - Marquand/football (Box 3)
      - Music annex (Box 3)
      - Yale Daily News banquet, SR 10 (Box 3)
      - Brewster swear-in, SR 19 (Box 3)
      - Commencement, SR 18, 1977 (Box 3)
      - Crew 1978, roll 17 (Box 3)
      - B-mix sync (Box 3)
      - Uncoded 1 (Box 3)
      - Teachers: Scully, Calabresi, Giamatti interview, The end (Box 3)
      - Inauguration, LZ (Box 4)
      - Law, Medicine, History; teachers (Box 4)
      - Scully, A la carte, Cricus, #9 (Box 4)
      - Sync roll outtakes (Box 4)
      - Teachers: Art, geology, Divinity (Box 4)
      - Freshman address, 1978 (Box 4)
      - Clerical, carpenters, glazier (Box 4)
      - "XOX" and Athletics (Box 4)
      - "A" (Box 4)
      - Freshman address, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Wild pix, wild sound, sync rolls (Box 4)
      - [W]ild Pix (Box 5)
      - Commencement (2 rolls), 1977 (Box 5)
      - press conference, president-elect Giamatti (Box 5)
      - Wild sound (Box 5)
      - #3 and #4 Weekend (Box 5)
      - commencement (2 rolls), 1977 (Box 5)
      - jamboree (Box 5)
      - weekend (Box 5)
      - Commencement, 1977 (Box 5)
      - search committee (Box 5)
      - Crew, Yale/Harvard, 1978 (Box 5)
      - search committee (sync roll) (Box 5)
      - tiny trims, box of (Box 5)
  - 275th Year
    - Sync rolls
      - Swim meet (Box 6)
      - Women's awards (Box 6)
      - Alumni house (Box 6)
      - 50th dinner (Box 6)
      - Dorm room and chemisty lab I (Box 6)
      - Campus exteriors (Box 6)
      - Coxe Cage and women's field hockey (Box 6)
      - Women's gymnastics (Box 6)
    - Mellon and register (Box 7)
      - MacLeish (Box 7)
      - Cole Porter (Box 7)
      - Woolsey Hall (Box 7)
      - Tennis and intramurals (Box 7)
      - Orchestra (Box 7)
      - Accelerator I & II (Box 7)
      - Basketball (Box 7)
      - Assorted wild films (Box 7)
      - Ballet (Box 8)
      - Drama (Box 8)
      - Lecture hall (Box 8)
      - Ice hockey (Box 8)
      - Polo (Box 8)
      - French table and band (Box 8)
      - Whiffenpoofs (Box 8)
      - Ford (Box 8)
    - Wild pix
      - Battel and Harkness aerial (Box 8)
      - MacLeish and Woolsey (Box 8)
    - Sync rolls
      - Soccer and tailgate (Box 9)
      - Football (Box 9)
      - Battel and Harkness (Box 9)
      - Beinecke and Art Gallery (Box 9)
  - Transition Year
    - 5 cuts (from release prints) of Abe Goldstein appointment (Box 9)
    - Final work print; dialogue 1 and 2; effects and narration tracks (Box 9)
    - Final sync track A and B; narration track; music track (Box 9)
  - 275th Year and Transition Year
    - Final work print (Box 10)
    - 1/4" tape of mix sound - final (Box 10)
    - Box of 1/4" tapes (Box 10)
    - Giamatti Kinescope and original (his talk "Story of Italy") (Box 10)
  - Walpole
    - Color work print (Box 11)
    - Sync rolls 1-5 (Box 11)
    - Mix tracks (Box 11)
    - Wild sound rolls (Box 11)
    - Lefty Lewis outtakes -pix (Box 11)
    - 1/4" tapes (Box 12)
    - Final work print (Box 12)
    - Pix (Box 12)
  - Transition Year
    - 1/4" tapes (Box 12)
  - Gym
    - Work print and mag. (Box 13)
    - Sound loops (Box 13)
    - Brief close-ups for open (Box 13)
    - Wild sounds -narration and trims (Box 13)
    - Wild sound -glee club (Box 13)
    - Sync roll
    - Wild pix -shower, diving, etc. (Box 13)
    - Wild sound, day 2 (Box 13)
    - 1/4" tapes (Box 13)
  - Indoor Exercise
    - Sound and pic outtakes (Box 14)
    - Work print (Box 14)
    - Mix rolls (Box 14)
  - Friday/Saturday (Weekend)
    - Wild sound (Box 15)
    - 1/4" tapes [Chaf] (Box 15)
    - Chafee speech -sync rolls (Box 15)
  - Child Study
    - Wild sound: Hill Health, Dr. Colmer (Box 15)
    - Sync rolls: Dr. Solnit's class, Dr. Colmer's interview, Provence test (Box 15)
    - Sync rolls: Hill Health, Nursery, Beth Haven Farm #2 (Box 16)
    - 1/4" tapes (Box 16)
    - Sound overlaps (Box 16)
  - Admissions
    - Work print (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
  - Child Study
    - Miscellaneous sounds and pictures (Box 17)
  - Transition Year
    - 1/4" tapes (also in box 12) (Box 18)
  - Child Study
    - Wild sound (Box 19)
    - Pix (Box 19)
  - Yale-in-China
    - Wild pix (Box 19)
    - Sync rolls (Box 19)
    - Work prints (Box 19)
  - Gerald Ford, Chubb Fellow
    - 1/4" tapes (Box 19)
  - Football highlights, 1978
    - Work print -Cozza (Box 19)
    - SEF's narration (Box 19)
  - Transition Year
    - Wild pix (Box 20)
    - Final outtakes (Box 20)
    - Work print (Box 20)
    - Wild sound (Box 21)
    - Protection sound track (after mix) (Box 22)
    - Wild pix -exteriors (Box 22)
    - Trims -wild and sync (Box 22)
  - Boswell
    - Slop print (Box 22)
    - Dialogue 1 and 2 (for mix) (Box 22)
    - Music (for mix) (Box 22)
    - Sound loops (Box 22)
    - Sync roll 1 (Box 22)
    - 1/4" tapes - actor (Boswell) and SEF (Box 22)
    - Wild sound and pix (all except what is listed in box 23 (Box 22)
    - Sync roll 2 (Box 23)
    - Wild Boswell (actor) -sound (Box 23)
    - Handel -music (Box 23)
    - Wild pix (Box 23)
    - Trims (tiny) -2 boxes (Box 23)
    - Outtakes -final editing -see 2 list for specifics (Box 23)
    - Animation -wild pix (Box 23)
    - Narration -wild sound (Box 23)
  - Paul Mellon visit, 1975 September
    - Wild sound (Box 23)
    - 1/4" tapes (Box 23)
  - School of Organization and Management opening
    - Sync roll (Box 23)
    - 1/4" tapes (Box 23)
    - Work print and mag (Box 23)
  - Ella Grasso (Chubb Fellow) (Box 23)
    - Work print (Box 24)
    - 1/4" tapes (Box 24)
    - Wild sounds (Box 24)
  - Moynihan
    - Wild sound (Box 24)
    - 1/4" tapes (Box 24)
    - Workprints (Box 25)
  - Mellon
    - Work prints, 1 (Box 25A)
    - Sync rolls, 1 (Box 25B)
    - Synchronized digital video with sound (from boxes 25A and 25B), 1
  - Story of Italy - "Machiavelli" by A.B. Giamatti
    - Quad videotape (Box 26)
  - Chubb Fellowship (Box 27)
  - Phil Garvan (not listed in original inventory) (Box 28)
- University Public Information motion picture films of Yale events and student life, circa 1969-1978; Accession 1980-A-001
  Scope and Contents
  Reappraised and processed by Barbara Fiddler and Stephen Cohen, 2002.
  Note: Films and production records listed below, were originally attributed to Yale University Films since Manuscripts and Archives staff packed up their records in 1991. Research on the films reveals them to come from various units on campus. Because of the medium, they all ended up at Yale University Films. The films are now reassigned to RUs that more accurately reflect their creation and original purpose.
  - Boswell work print (900'), Circa 1975; film reel (16mm) (Box 1)
  - Walpole (1000'), 1976; film reel (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Giamatti Inauguration/Graduation, 1978
    - Old Campus (Box 6, Box 27–28, Box 30)
    - Crowd in Front of Woodbridge Hall (Box 18)
    - Dinner in Commons (Box 8, Box 16, Box 22–23)
    - Interview (close up of Giamatti) (Box 25, Box 32)
    - Giamatti speaking (Box 9)
    - Giamatti inauguration, 1978 (Box 26, Box 33)
    - Speech in President's Room, Woolsey Hall (Box 10)
    - Reception in Garden of President's House (Box 7, Box 17, Box 20, Box 29, Box 31)
    - Hanna Gray Interview (Box 34–36)
    - Football Game (Box 11–12)
    - Aerial Views of Campus (Box 13–15)
    - Street Hall Banner "Welcome Class of 1982" (Box 24)
  - Yale: The 275th Year, answer print (1000'), 1976; film reel (16mm) (Box 3)
  - Campaign For Yale, answer print (1200'), 1974; film reel (16mm) (Box 4)
  - Winter Scene on Elm Street (200'), Circa 1969; film reel (16mm) (Box 5)
  - Front of Peabody Museum (225'), Circa 1978 (Box 21)
  - Architectural Details (310'), Circa 1978; film reel (16mm) (Box 19)
  - May 1st Protesters on Green, work print (1000'), 1969; film reel (16mm) (Box 47)
  - Coed, Graduation (300'), 1969 June 8; film reel (16mm) (Box 37)
  - Students Playing Frisbee on Old Campus (200'), 1969; film reel (16mm) (Box 38)
  - New Haven Green Vending Truck & Protesters (300'), Circa 1969; film reel (16mm) (Box 39)
  - Football Game (Cornell) in Yale Bowl (300'), Circa 1969; film reel (16mm) (Box 40)
  - Graduation Crowd in Beinecke Plaza (250'), Circa 1969; film reel (16mm) (Box 41)
  - Branford Courtyard, Entrance to Pierson (100'), Circa 1969; film reel (16mm) (Box 42)
  - Autumn Friday/Saturday (400'), 1975; film reel (16mm) (Box 43)
  - Autumn Friday/Saturday, work print (400'), 1975; film reel (16mm) (Box 44)
  - Mellon Center Construction Site (200'), circa 1976; 2 (Box 45–46)
    - Use copy for boxes 45-46, optical disk (DVD) (Box 45U)
  - Organization and Man (650' each), Circa 1976; 2 (Box 48–49)
  - Yale: One Perspective, An Admission Film (800' each), 1974; 2 (Box 50–51)
  - Admissions (700'), 1974 April; film reel (16mm) (Box 52)
- Videorecordings documenting Yale University, 1966-2008; Accession 2009-A-156
  Conditions Governing Access
  Most of the audiovisual items in this accession are commercially-produced. Copies of commercially-produced items cannot be made for researcher use outside of the repository.
  - 3415: 100th Anniversary Harvard vs. Yale Football Game, 1983 December 5; 1 (Box 957)
  - 3390: Volunteers, 1985 July 18; 1 (Box 291)
  - 3893: Commencement Clips, various, 1986-1998; 1 (Box 964)
  - 3353: President Giamatti / Yale University, 1986 June 6; 1 (Box 261)
  - 3514: The Way It Was, Harvard University's 250th Anniversary, 1986 September 3; 1 (Box 364)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 364U)
  - 3320: Positively Connecticut: Yale's Elizabethan Club, 1986 December 29; 1 (Box 228)
  - 3671: Conservation Story with Millicent Abel, 1987 March 23; 1 (Box 446)
  - 3352: Racist groups, 1987 April 2; 1 (Box 260)
  - 3487: TV News Coverage of Contract Negotiations, 1988 January 12; 1 (Box 343)
  - 3488: Yale Clerical Strike, 1988 January 12; 1 (Box 344)
  - 3311: Eccentric Books, 1988 February 1; 1 (Box 219)
  - 3326: Babylonian Tablets, 1988 March 28; 1 (Box 234)
  - 3887: Amy Ruschak - Dr. LaMotte, 1988 April 21; 1 (Box 959)
  - 3347: Aroma Therapy, 1988 May 2; 1 (Box 255)
  - 3325: Halftime: 5 Yale Men in Midlife, 1988 June 2; 1 (Box 233)
  - 3321: Preserving Books, 1988 June 12; 1 (Box 229)
  - 3323: Shelia Wellington Coalition Against Apartied, 1988 June 20; 1 (Box 231)
  - 3348: The Wall Controversy, 1988 June 20; 1 (Box 256)
  - 3349: Security Week at Yale, 1989 February 1; 1 (Box 257)
  - 3339: Animal Rights Rally at Yale, 1989 April 22; 1 (Box 247)
  - 3350: New Zealand Prime Minister Lange, 1989 April 24; 1 (Box 258)
  - 4185: Robotic Juggling Tasks, 1989 August 1; 1 (Box 796)
  - 3338: Tribute to Bart Giamatti, 1989 September 1; 1 (Box 246)
  - 3289: Death of Bart Giamatti, 1989 September 1-2; 1 (Box 197)
  - 3291: Washington University Lecture Series #3 AIDS, 1989 September 25; 1 (Box 199)
  - 3297: Gay/Lesbian Rally at Yale, WFSB and WTNH, 1989 October 30; 1 (Box 205)
  - 3669: Gay/Lesbian Rally at Yale, investigation of police brutality during rally, 1989 October 30; 1 (Box 902)
  - 3279: Rhodes Scholars From Yale, 1989 December 11; 1 (Box 187)
  - 3686: Terrorism Technology, 1990; 1 (Box 459)
  - 3283: Mike Roemer Yale Film Professor, 1990 February 6; 1 (Box 191)
  - 3259: Michael Roemer, 1990 February 11; 1 (Box 171)
  - 3250: Chikyu Hokoku Special, 1990 February 18; 1 (Box 163)
  - 3248: Tax on Non - Education Properties, WTNH, 1990 March 13; 1 (Box 161)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 161U)
  - 3282: Protesters Greet Sec. Richard Cheney at Yale, 1990 April 19; 1 (Box 190)
  - 4227: Yale Rebuilds: Calhoun College, 1990 May 4; 1 (Box 828)
  - 3298: Bass Donation to Yale, 1990 May 8; 1 (Box 206)
  - 4280: Sandra's Graduation, edited copy, 1990 May 11; 1 (Box 865)
  - 3245: Project Demos, Good Morning America, 1990 May 21; 1 (Box 158)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 158U)
  - 3271: The World is Calling, 1990 July 29; 1 (Box 181)
  - 3285: Yale's 290th Year, 1990 August 31; 1 (Box 193)
  - 3255: Habitat for Humanity, WTNH, 1990 September 6; 1 (Box 167)
  - 3540: Yale School of Forestry and Env. Studies: A Leading Tradition, 1991 January 1; 1 (Box 382)
  - 3293: Comic Strip Live, 1991 January 29; 1 (Box 201)
  - 3266: Comic Strip Live, 1991 February 11; 1 (Box 177)
  - 3264: A Closer Look: "Campus Crime", 1991 February 20; 1 (Box 176)
  - 3234: Politically Correct, 1991 May 13; 1 (Box 150)
  - 3231: NPC: Schmidt, 1991 June 4; 1 (Box 147)
  - 3204: Brownell, 1991 June 27; 1 (Box 125)
  - 3230: ABC Dieting, 1991 June 27; 1 (Box 146)
  - 3233: NBC and CBS Dieting, 1991 June 27; 1 (Box 149)
  - 3247: Technophobia, 1991 November 13; 1 (Box 160)
  - 3412: L.E.A.P. Final Report, 1992; 1 (Box 310)
  - 3395: Bill Reilly Speech, 1992 April 21; 1 (Box 296)
  - 4187: Yale Promo, Telesis Productions, 1992 April 30; 1 (Box 798)
  - 3249: Yale Campaign Launch, 1992 May 2; 1 (Box 162)
  - 3246: Space Shuttle Droplet Search, 1992 July 6; 1 (Box 159)
  - 4028: Charlie Rose/President Levin, 1993; 1 (Box 653)
  - 4230: Richard Levin Announcement for President, 1993 Spring; 1 (Box 831)
  - 4277: Stephanie Klasky and Steven Gamer, Video Designs, 1993 January 17; 1 (Box 862)
  - 3310: Class of '68 - 25th Year Reunion, 1993 May 1; 1 (Box 218)
  - 3318: High-Tech Shower International, 1993 September 13; 1 (Box 226)
  - 3251: Nanocomputers, 1993 September 27; 1 (Box 164)
  - 3307: Scienctific American Frontiers, 1993 October 1; 1 (Box 215)
  - 3406: Levin Presidential Announcement / Hillary Clinton Speech, 1993 October 1; 1 (Box 304)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 304U)
  - 4231: Richard Levin's Inauguration, 1993 October 2; 1 (Box 832)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 832U)
  - 3342: Richard Levin's Inauguration, 1993 October 2; 1; Duplicating Master (VHS) (Box 250)
    - Use copy, Optical Disk (DVD) (Box 250U)
  - 3273: Presentation of Medal of Merit to President Clinton, 1993 October 9; 1 (Box 183)
  - 3299: Richard Levin/Yale President, 1993 October 22; 1 (Box 207)
  - 3262: A Unique Medical Education, 1993 December 14; 1 (Box 174)
  - 3434: Yale Band in the Glenn Miller tradition, 1994; 1 (Box 876)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 876U)
  - 3393: New Haven: An Emerging Center for Biotechnology, 1994 January 1; 1 (Box 294)
  - 3411: Yale Promo tape 1994, 1994 January 1; 1 (Box 309)
  - 3512: A Harvard Day, 1994 January 1; 1 (Box 362)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 362U)
  - 3181: Violence in America/New Haven, 1994 January 9; 1 (Box 105)
  - 3304: Today's Breakthroughs: Tomorrow's Cures, 1994 March 1; 1 (Box 212)
  - 3358: Athletic Director Announcement, 1994 April 11; 1 (Box 266)
  - 3888: New Athletic Director at Yale, 1994 April 11; 1 (Box 941)
  - 3182: Spiders, 1994 April 29; 1 (Box 106)
  - 3388: Donations from China, 1994 May 1; 1 (Box 290)
  - 3253: Baccalaureate Address, 1994 May 22; 1 (Box 166)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 166U)
  - 3272: Panel on Information Super Hwy, 1994 May 27; 1 (Box 182)
  - 3341: Yale Class of 1969 Panel on New Haven, 1994 May 27; 1 (Box 249)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 249U)
  - 3416: Class of 1969 Panel: Information Super Highway, 1994 May 27; 1 (Box 932)
  - 3267: Yale University Band--WWII style, 1994 May 29; 1 (Box 178)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 178U)
  - 3337: New Haven Update - Association of Yale Alumni, 1994 May 29; 1 (Box 245)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 245U)
  - 3432: Yale Band, 1994 May 29; 1 (Box 323)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 323U)
  - 3295: Yale Campaign School for Women, 1994 July 3; 1 (Box 203)
  - 3403: Yale In Vitro, 1994 July 20; 1 (Box 303)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 303U)
  - 3489: Yale Promo tape 1994, 1994 August 1; 1 (Box 345)
  - 3324: Yale in the News, famous actors, Yale band, etc., 1994 September 15; 1 (Box 232)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 232U)
  - 3327: New Haven Alderman Meeting, 1994 September 26; 1 (Box 235)
  - 3328: New Haven: A Growing Center for Biotechnology, 1994 October 5; 1 (Box 236)
  - 3501: Yale Promo tape 1994, campus scenes and narration, 1994 November 9; 1 (Box 350)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 350U)
  - 3553: 1995 Special Olympics Opening Ceremonies, 1 (Box 394)
  - 3330: Teaching on Common Ground, 1995 January 1; 1 (Box 238)
  - 3333: Changing Lives - Yale China Association, 1995 January 1; 1 (Box 241)
  - 3397: Bass Donation to Yale, 1995 January 1; 1 (Box 298)
  - 3303: Donald Kagan, Yale University, 1995 January 13; 1 (Box 211)
  - 3183: Giuliani at Yale, 1995 January 18; 1 (Box 107)
  - 3309: Stephanie O'Malley, Yale School of Medicine, 1995 January 18; 1 (Box 217)
  - 3334: TechnoPolitics #443, 1995 January 20; 1 (Box 242)
  - 3317: TechnoPolitics, 1995 January 21; 1 (Box 225)
  - 3301: Yale Brain Language Study, 1995 February 1; 1 (Box 209)
  - 3322: Yale in the News, 1995 February 6; 1 (Box 230)
  - 3394: Family Campus Meeting, 1995 February 8; 1 (Box 295)
  - 3315: Yale Fruitfly Study, 1995 February 10; 1 (Box 223)
  - 3335: TechnoPolitics High-Tech Shower, 1995 February 21; 1 (Box 243)
  - 3661: Problems with Statistics, 1995 March 21; 1 (Box 437)
  - 3302: Yale Imposter Expelled, 1995 April 1; 1 (Box 210)
  - 3398: US 1 Tour 1-3, 1995 May 1; 1 (Box 299)
  - 3410: US 1 Tour 4-6, 1995 May 1; 1 (Box 308)
  - 3306: Inside Space (Sci Fi channel), 1995 May 14; 1 (Box 214)
  - 3300: Bass Contribution to Yale, 1995 May 26; 1 (Box 208)
  - 3292: Currents of Fear, 1995 June 13; 1 (Box 200)
  - 3296: Special Olympics, 1995 June 15; 1 (Box 204)
  - 3313: Special Olympics, 1995 June 18; 1 (Box 221)
  - 3269: Special Olympics, 1995 July 3; 1 (Box 180)
  - 3268: Special Olympics Opening Ceremony, 1995 July 5; 1 (Box 179)
  - 3319: Yale in the News, 1995 June 30 - July 3; 1 (Box 227)
  - 3901: Special Olympics Tennis Player, CBS This Morning, 1995 July 7; 1 (Box 553)
  - 3821: New Haven Ravens, WTIC and WTNH, 1995 August 1; 1 (Box 734)
  - 3822: Volvo Tennis Tournament, SNET Tennis Classic, New Haven Ravens, ESPN and WTNH, 1995 August 2-26; 1 (Box 958)
  - 3274: Special Olympics, 1995 August 31; 1 (Box 184)
  - 3229: Benjamin Bolger, Today Show, NBC, 1995 September 25; 1 (Box 145)
  - 3359: Eye on Business, 1995 October 1; 1 (Box 267)
  - 3232: Richard Levin/Yale President, 1995 October 8; 1 (Box 148)
  - 3184: Bromley, 1995 October 18; 1 (Box 108)
  - 3202: John Butler/Miracles, 1995 November 1; 1 (Box 123)
  - 3346: Yale Library Renovations, 1995 November 29; 1 (Box 254)
  - 3354: David Saltzman, 1995 December 13; 1 (Box 262)
  - 3356: The Real Richard Nixon, 1995 December 20; 1 (Box 264)
  - 3261: Movies In Time: "Nixon", 1995 December 22; 1 (Box 173)
  - 4211: Old Campus, 1996; 1 (Box 813)
  - 3288: Yale Labor Disputes, 1996 January 11; 1 (Box 196)
  - 3355: Pass It On, 1996 February 2; 1 (Box 263)
  - 3281: State of the State, 1996 February 7; 1 (Box 189)
  - 3260: The Diane Payton Show, 1996 February 25; 1 (Box 172)
  - 3205: Hunchback of Notre Dame, 1996 April 1; 1 (Box 126)
  - 3206: Religious Expression at Work, "Sports Violence", 1996 April 1; 1 (Box 127)
  - 3207: Women's Campaign School, 1996 April 1; 1 (Box 128)
  - 3244: Fad Diets, 1996 April 1; 1 (Box 157)
  - 3277: Henry Winkler, Yale Class Day Speaker, 1996 April 26; 1 (Box 930)
  - 3294: High-Tech Shower International, 1996 May 1; 1 (Box 202)
  - 3897: High Tech Shower, Robert Crabtree and Pat Sharp, 1996 May 1; 1 (Box 550)
  - 3252: Robotics (Episode 9613), 1996 May 3; 1 (Box 165)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 165U)
  - 3286: Yale Skull and Bones Society, 1996 May 8; 1 (Box 194)
  - 3258: Charles Remington/Cicadas, Today Show, 1996 May 11; 1 (Box 170)
  - 3257: Charles Remington/Cicadas, Good Morning America, 1996 June 1; 1 (Box 169)
  - 3345: Yale Campaign School for Women, 1996 June 1; 1 (Box 253)
  - 3408: See Jane Run, 1996 June 1; 1 (Box 306)
  - 3284: Dr. Remington, Cicadas, 1996 June 9; 1 (Box 192)
  - 3200: Yale Architecture Project, 1996 August 1; 1 (Box 121)
  - 3343: Phony Document Fraud / Identity Theft, 1996 September 4; 1 (Box 251)
  - 3357: Yale Campaign School for Women, 1996 September 22; 1 (Box 265)
  - 3768: Charter Day Celebration, 1996 October 25; 1 (Box 474)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 474U)
  - 3366: Pesticides - John Wargo, 1996 November 1; 1 (Box 273)
  - 3673: High Tech Shower International, 1996 November 1; 1 (Box 448)
  - 3344: Yale Coach - Carm Cozza, 1996 November 24; 1 (Box 252)
  - 3391: Carmen Cozza (Football Coach) Steps Down, 1996 November 24; 1 (Box 292)
  - Middle Class College, 1; This item was incorrectly labelled by the Yale Office of Public Affairs as "3371: Robotics, Optics, Resonators, RNA, 1996 December 1." (Box 277)
    Related Materials
    See: 3985: STN Show #1204, Robotics, Optic, Resonators, RNA
  - 3985: STN Show #1204, Robotics, Optic, Resonators, RNA, 1996 December 1; 1 (Box 620)
  - 4008: PSS, APCO Associates, Inc., 1996 December 12; 1 (Box 642)
  - 3361: Labor Agreement, 1996 December 19; 1 (Box 269)
  - 3513: ...and for Yale, 1997 January 1; 1 (Box 363)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 363U)
  - 3362: C-Span School Bus Winter ' 96, 1997 January 1; 1 (Box 270)
  - 3363: Cambodian Genocide, 1997 January 1; 1 (Box 271)
  - 3363: Kelly Brownell on fat tax, CNN, 1997 July 31; 1 (Box 872)
  - 3550: 13th Annual Forestry School Doctoral Research Conference, Tape 1, 1997 February 7; 1 (Box 391)
  - 3551: 13th Annual Forestry School Doctoral Research Conference, Tape 2, 1997 February 7; 1 (Box 392)
  - 3201: Movies In Time, 1997 March 1; 1 (Box 122)
  - 3375: Friends of Franklin Papers, 1997 May 18; 1 (Box 281)